You can’t run from who you are.
Bones and All is a horror, romance, drama film directed by Luca Guadagnino.
Abandoned by her father, a young woman embarks on a thousand-mile odyssey through
the backroads of America where she meets a disenfranchised drifter.
But despite their best efforts, all roads lead back to their terrifying pasts and to a final
stand that will determine whether their love can survive their otherness.
Maren, played by Taylor Russell.
Lee, played by Timothée Chalamet.
Sully, played by Mark Rylance.
Kayla, played by Anna Cobb.
Maren's Father, played by André Holland.
Brad, played by David Gordon Green.
Bones and All is a 2022 romantic horror film directed by Luca Guadagnino from a screenplay by
David Kajganich, based on the 2015 novel Bones & All by Camille DeAngelis.
Set in the late 1980s, the film stars Taylor Russell and Timothée Chalamet as a pair of young
cannibals who develop feelings for each other on a road trip across the United States.
Michael Stuhlbarg, André Holland, Chloë Sevigny, David Gordon Green, Jessica
Harper, Jake Horowitz, and Mark Rylance appear in supporting roles.
Bones and All had its world premiere at the 79th Venice International Film Festival on September 2, 2022,
where it won the Silver Lion for best direction and the Marcello Mastroianni Award for Russell.
The film was released theatrically in the United States on November 18 by United Artists
Releasing's Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Pictures, and elsewhere by Warner Bros.
Pictures, with the exception of Italy, where it was
distributed by Vision Distribution.
It is the first MGM film to be distributed internationally by Warner Bros.
under their new multi year international theatrical distribution pact with
MGM, following MGM's previous deal with Universal Pictures.
The film received positive reviews, with critics praising the performances of Russell, Chalamet, and
Rylance, Guadagnino's direction, the cinematography, score, and fusion of genres.
It received a variety of award nominations, including Best Feature, Best Lead Performance for
Russell, and Best Supporting Performance for Rylance at the 38th Independent Spirit Awards.
However, it underperformed at the box office, grossing $15.2
million against a production budget of $16–20 million.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, sense of
guilt, homelessness, addiction, road trip.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.